A Guide to the Rodman C. Rockefeller papers FA1350
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rodman C. Rockefeller papers
1929-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Rodman (1932-2000)
Durr, Kenneth D.
FA1350
37.29 Cubic Feet 91 letter document boxes, 3 legal document boxes, and 1 standard record storage box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net wealth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center by Alexandra (Sascha) Rockefeller.
Biographical / Historical
Rodman Clark Rockefeller (May 2, 1932 – May 14, 2000) was an American businessman, philanthropist, and philanthropic administrator. He was the eldest son of former Nelson Aldrich Rockefeller and Mary Todhunter Clark.
Rodman Rockefeller attended Dartmouth College, and conducted graduated studies at Columbia for which he earned a master's degree in business administration. He served as a trustees for a variety of institutions including but not limited to: the America's Society, the Institute of International Education, the Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation, the Museum of Modern Art, the New York Blood Center and the Rockefeller Brothers Fund.
He also served as a trustee of Rockefeller Financial Services, which manages the Rockefeller family's office (known as "Room 5600") and Rockefeller and Company.
Rockefeller also served as co-chairman of the Mexico-United States Business Committee, an organization focused on economic, political, and cultural relations that was significantly involved in advocating for what ultimately became the North American Free Trade Association (NAFTA).
Rodman Rockefeller also had a long association with the International Basic Economy Corporation for which he served as vice president (1968 to 1972), chief executive (1972 to 1980), and chairman of its successor organization IBEC, Inc. (1980-1985).
Scope and Contents
The collection primarily consists of personal and professional correspondence, board records and supporting materials, trip files, speeches, remarks, and records of personal and political contributions. Rodman Rockefeller's diverse interests and activities are well represented including documentation of his involvement with the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC), Pocantico Development Associates, Arbor Acres Farm, the Institute of International Education (IIE), Dartmouth College, and the Museum of Modern Art.
There is also a small selection of research materials from Kenneth Durr (Series VI) pertaining to his work on the history of IBEC, including IBEC annual reports and a compliation of chronological correspondence from Mr. Rockefeller.
Arrangement
Loosely arranged in six series as follows:
Series I: Business Interests
Series II: Cultural Interests
Series III: Personal Interests
Series IV: Political Interests
Series V: Educational Interests
Series VI: Kenneth Durr Research Materials
- Business Interests, 1960-2001; I; 10.53 Cubic Feet 24 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - The Conference Board: North American International Conference: YAMA Series - Itinterary, 1987 February 12-17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - IBEC: Sir George Bishop Dinner, 1982 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mexico - United States Business Committee - 43rd Plenary Meeting, 1988 November 17-18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - U.S. - Mexico Businessman's Committee, 32nd Plenary Meeting, 1977 November 16-19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - U.S. - Mexico Businessman's Committee Plenary Meetings - Trip Itinerary, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - U.S. - Mexico Businessman's Committee Meetings - Background Information for Meetings, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - IBEC - International Basic Economy Corporation - Trip to Brazil, 1980 February 10-25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Interractial Council for Business Opportunity - Annual Dinner, 1981 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Magsaysay Awards, Bangkok, 1987 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation from the President of Brazil, 1995 April 21 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pocantico Associates Inc. - Business Meeting, San Antonio Museum Event, 1998 October 21-24 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family is restricted.
  - U.S. - Mexico Commision, 1997 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller and Co. - Conference, 1999 February 21-24 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Metzler Symposium - Frankfurt, Germany, September 16, 1997; Trip to Munich, Germany, September 18 -19, 1997, 1997 September (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - U.S. - Mexican Commission, 15th Reunion, 1997 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - U.S. - Mexican Committee Meeting - 50th Annual Plenary Meeting - Houston, Texas, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Booker Board Meeting and Retirement Dinner, 1996 April 28-May 4 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Aquila Azteca Award Dinner - Mexico City, Mexico, 1996 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Palm Beach, Florida, 1996 January 31-February 4 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Booker Board Meeting - London, England, September 30-October 6, 1995, Venice, Italy - October 6-12, 1995, 1995 September-October (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Booker Board Meeting, 1995 October 10-15 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Senior Executive Conference, Westminster - Arbor Acres Farm (AAF) Board Meeting - London, England - April 17-19, 1991 and Paris, France - April 19-22, 1991, 1991 April (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rock and Co. Investments Meeting (Itinerary) - Mexico City, Mexico, 1990 December 3-7 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. Picnic - Winterburn, 1992 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Council of the Mexico - U.S. Business Committee: Canada Trip - Toronto, Includes Trip Itinerary and Report, 1992 July 1-5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc. - East-Central Europe Trip, 1991 October 10-20 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Housatonic Partners Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Housatonic Partners Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Personnel Policy, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Branch and Associates - Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Background Statements, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Jacek Makowski - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Barbanchano Hotels, Yucatan - Mexico, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Barbanchano Hotels, Yucatan - Mexico, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1981 October-1982 December (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1983 January-August (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1986 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1991 January-June (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1991 July-December (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1992 January-June (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1992 July-December (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Amendment to Certificate of Incorporation, 1993 July 21 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Correspondence, 1997 October-November (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medical Computers, Inc. - Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws, 1985 February 27 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medical Computers, Inc. - Copyright, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medical Computers, Inc. - Trademark Search, 1985 March (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medical Computers, Inc. - Shareholders and Capital Stock, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Thermo Electron Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medical Computers Inc., Medigest Software, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medigest Brochure (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medical Computers, Inc. - Chronological File, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico Development Associates, Inc. - Medical Computers, Inc. - Chronological File, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Medical Computers, Inc. - Chronological File, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Medical Computers, Inc. - Chronological File, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Medical Computers, Inc. - Chronological File, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Medical Computers, Inc. - Chronological File, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Medical Computers, Inc. - Chronological File, 1990 October 19 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Optimal Energy System, Inc. (PDAI) - Stocks, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Tractionel S.A. - Belgium, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Background Statements, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Corporate Reorganization, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Medical Property Investors, (Executive Summary) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Status Report, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1993 August 3 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1994 January-June (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1994 July-December (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1995 January-June (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1995 July-December (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1996 January-June (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1996 July-December (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1997 January-June (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronlogical File, 1997 July-December (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1998 January-June (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1998 July-December (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Pocantico Associates, Inc. - Chronological File, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Restricted - Confidential material
  - Minority Equity Capital Company, Inc. - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Minority Equity Capital Company, Inc. - Auditors Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Minority Equity Capital Company, Inc. - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity - Dinners and Luncheons, 1980-1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity - Correspondence, 1966-1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity - Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity - Rodman C. Rockefeller Contributions, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity - Articles, Brochures and Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Arbor Acres Farm and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Arbor Acres Farm and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Arbor Acres Farm and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Arbor Acres Farm and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Chronological File, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation and Booker Plc. - Litigation Related NTBF Accounts Receivable, 1992 February-April (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Booker Plc.: Charles J. Bowen - Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Booker Plc.: Jonathan F. Taylor - Correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Booker Plc.: Jonathan F. Taylor - Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Booker Plc.: Restructure, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Booker Plc.: Audit Committee, 1991 July-December (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lowell Hoskins, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Miscellaneous Financial Correspondence, 1984 July-November (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Miscellaenous Share Holder's Correspondence, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Aquaculture Correspondence, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Arbor Acres Fishery Correspondence, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Miscellaenous Arbor Acre Correspondence and a 1990 Gift to Dartmouth (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Miscellaneous Financial Correspondence, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Booker Plc.: Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Booker Plc.: Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Booker Plc.: Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - The United States Agricultural Development Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - The United States Agricultural Development Corporation, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - The United States Agricultural Development Corporation, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - The United States Agricultural Development Corporation, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Booker Plc. - Arbor Acres Farm - Shareholders Agreement, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Booker Plc. - Arbor Acres Farm - Shareholders Agreement, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Booker Plc. - Shareholders Agreement, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Booker Plc. Finances, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Booker Agribusiness Limited, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Iran Development and Resources Corporation Claims, 1983-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Iran Development and Resources Corporation Claims, 1983-1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Booker Agricultural International - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Mexico, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Puerto Rico, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968-1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Booker Merger and Reorganization, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Booker Merger and Reorganization, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Booker Merger and Reorganization, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Arbor Acres Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Arbor Acres Publicity, 1965; 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Water Holdings, Incorporated, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Arbor Acres - James D. Nelson Correspondence, 1991 -1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Arbor Acres Farm - Pennie and Edmonds, 1987 October 22-26 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Sale of Booker Shares, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Sale of Booker Shares, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Warburg Securities, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Warburg Securities, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Booker: Director's Responsibilities and Fees, 1985-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Board Meetings, 1985-1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Board Meetings, 1985-1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Arbor Acres Farm: Shares, 1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Arbor Acres Farm: Shares, 1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Booker: Charles Sharpe and Company, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Reorganization of Agri-Finance, 1983; 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Arbor Acres Farm - Reorganization, 1985 November-December (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Amgen Inc., 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Arbor Acres Farm - Salmon and Trout Farming, 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Development and Resource Corporation, 1983-1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Development and Resource Corporation, 1983-1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Genetics, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Arbor Acres Farm - Retirement Plan, 1981-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Restricted - Personnel material
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Arbor Acres Farm: Employees, 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Booker Board Meetings, 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Somalia, Africa, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Arbor Acres - Nicholas Scientific Conference, 1980 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - International Basic Economy Conference, Genetics, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Biotechnologies, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Biotechnologies, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Arbor Acres Farm - Nicholas Turkey Breeding Farm, 1978-1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Arbor Acres Farm, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Genetics Articles, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Venezuela Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Venezuela - Sale of CADA and Judibana, 1969-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Memorandum to the Board of Directors on Alternative Courses of Corporate Action, 1978 September 13 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Memorandum to the Board of Directors on Alternative Courses of Corporate Action (Statistica Exhibit), 1978 September 13 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Summary on Proposed Corporate Reorganization, Core of Agribusiness Assets, 1979 January 5 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Summary on Proposed Corporate Reorganization, Core of Agribusiness Assets "Agribec", 1979 January 15 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Operations Workshop, 1972; 1974 October-November (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc. - Acquisition, Effective December 7, 1984, By BookBec, Inc. of Shares of Class B Common Stock of IBEC, Inc. and Merger, Effective December 31, 1984 of Booker Oil Services, Inc. into BookBec, Inc. and Acquisitions, Effective February 21, 1985, by Booker McConnell PLC of Shares of Class B Common Stock of IBEC Inc., and Merger, Effective March 1, 1985, of Arbor Acres Farm, Inc. into IBEC, Inc. and Incorporation Effective March, 1, 1985 of IBEC, Inc. and Merger, Effective March 13, 1985 of Arbor Acres Farm, Inc. into BookBeck, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Boards of Directorship (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Boards of Directorship (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller and Co., Inc., 1991-1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller - Prospective Boards, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Group, Inc. - Rockefeller Center, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation Stock, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation-Makro, SHV Holdings, Netherlands, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "The Prospect for the US Property Market", Metzler Bank Conference, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Long Range Planning Committee for Room 5600, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Restricted - Security documentation
  - Rockefeller Group Inc., Correspondence, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Group Inc., Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Group Inc., Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Financial Services, Chairmanship, 1991-1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Financial Services - Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - The Vidas Acapulco Project - Legal Box, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Association of American Chambers of Commerce in Latin America - XI Corporate Briefing Session - Speech, Luncheon, Mexico - Mexus, 1981 April 22 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Reciprocity of Needs - Mutuality of Interests, March 19, 1980, Doing Business With Mexico - Luncheon Address, November 12, 1980, Mexico - Mexus, 1980 March (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Busco, Inc., Arbor Acres Farm Inc., Annual Report, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc., Annual Report, 1987 December 31 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc., Annual Report, 1988 December 31 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc., Annual Report, 1990 December 31 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc., Annual Report, 1991 December 28 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc., Annual Report, 1992 December 26 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Booker McConnell PLC, Reports and Accounts, 1981; 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Booker McConnell PLC, Reports and Accounts, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)